

abdulkareem.fallaha.mnv@gmail. com

+963 96 917 3279



Aleppo, Syria



www.abdulkareemfallaha website

linkedin.com/in/abdulkareemfallaha-241068137



twitter.com/AbdulkareemFal2



aboood.asq



facebook.com/abdulkareem.abd ulkareem.54540218

SKILLS

PHP

Laravel

HTML5



wordpress

MySQL

Python

Web Development

Project Management

LANGUAGES

English











Abdulkareem Fallaha

Software Engineer

Experienced Web Specialist and Quality Assurance Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python, Java, PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, and jQuery. Strong media and communication professional graduated from University of Aleppo.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Quality Assurance

Automata4 Group

08/2015 - 07/2018Aleppo , Syria

Automata4 Group is a Syria-based company dedicated to providing high quality customg IT solutions and Consulting services

Full Stack Developer

CLIC Agency

08/2018 - 01/2019 Damascus, Syria

CLIC is a marketing and branding agency. From branding, web design and development to social media to social media, marketing strategies, planning

Full Stack Developer

GivingLoop

02/2019 - Present Amman, Jordan

GivingLoop aims to disrupt how nonprofits raise funds and become sustainable. https://www.givingloop.org/

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Laravel Builder (07/2017 - Present)

Website that gives programmers tools to build websites with laravel back-end, Bootstrap front-end

Al-Bakkar Trading Company (10/2018 - 12/2018)

Website for Al-Bakkar Trading Company. www.bakkar-trd.com

EDUCATION

Information Technology University of Aleppo

10/2012 - 04/2018

Aleppo, Syria - GPA (77.9)

Master Web Science Syrian Virtual University

05/2018 - Present

Aleppo, Syria

ORGANIZATIONS

Syrian Computer Society (05/2018 - Present)

Syrian Engineers Syndicate (05/2018 - Present)

CERTIFICATES

Bachelor of Technology - BTech GPA (77.9) (04/2018 - Present)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Web Development workshop at Informatics Faculty (02/2019 - 02/2019)

Workshop in web development at Informatics Faculty, Key Words: (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP)

Web Development workshop at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo) (03/2019 - 03/2019)

Workshop in web development at Syria Trust (Shabab Aleppo), Key Words: (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP)